# Hernan Lorenzo

# Full Stack Developer

✓ lorenzoestebanhernan@gmail.com

in Hernan Lorenzo 🦪 Hlorenzoo

📍 Tucumán, Argentina

(C) +543816977428

Portfolio

#### Education

Full Stack Developer - Plataforma 5, 800+ hour theoretical and practical program, implementing Scrum and Pair Programming methodologies. React · Redux · React Native · NodeJs · Express · Sequelize · Postgress · Git · Trello ☑ 06/2022 - 10/2022

# **Programming Fundamentals -**

Plataforma 5, *JavaScript · HTML · CSS · Bootstrap · Objects · Classes · DOM manipulation* ☑ 04/2022 – 06/2022

## Industrial Engineering, More than 30

approved subjects. Studies up to the fourth year of the career. - Facultad de Ciencias Exactas y Tecnología, Universidad Nacional de Tucumán.

2015 - 2020

#### Skills

JavaScript | Node.js | Express.js | MongoDB | Mongoose | PostgreSQL | Sequelize | JWT |RESTful API | Docker | Strapi |

React.js | Next.js | Redux | ChakraUI | MaterialUI | SASS | Bootstrap | Vercel | Git | Github |

# Languages

English : Advanced ☑(C2) Spanish : Native

#### About me

Since I was a child I have always had a passion for technology, and this led me to challenge myself and do a Coding Bootcamp, where I found in programming what motivates me to keep myself in constant learning.

In my years of work experience what I value the most are the aptitudes and skills developed in pursuit of excellent teamwork and a fully satisfied customer.

# Web Development Experience

#### Hogarth Wordwide, WOW Magazine

09/2022 - 10/2022

Group project developing a web page for a female oriented magazine. The site has completly dynamic desing and all sections can be laid ouy according to editorial needs. Development and Ux/UI design of an interactive widget, connecting the user's chosen emotion with recommended articles to increse site traffic.

Technologies involved : Node.js, Next.js , ChakraUI, Strapi, MongoDB.

## Plataforma 5, SmartStore

09/2022 - 09/2022

Two weeks group project developing an e-commerce for a ficticional gamer company. Available features include cookie based authentication, search, filters, favorites, cart, reviews,

Technologies involved : Node.js, Express, MongoDB, React.js, MUI.

rating, purchase history, mail sale confirmation.

#### Plataforma 5, TMDB

09/2022 - 09/2022

One week individual project, developing a movie and tv show catalogue web application consuming TMDB's API. Available features include cookie based authentication, search, filters and favorites.

Technologies involved : Node.js, Express, MongoDB, React.js, MUI.

## Other Experiences

## Call center agent, Aegis Argentina

04/2019 - 12/2020 | Tucumán, Argentina

#### **Building Manager**

01/2017 - 01/2019 | Tucumán, Argentina

Lift Operator, *Tahoe Donner Association* 11/2015 – 04/2016 | Truckee California, Estados Unidos